Federico Pozzi

14-oct-1995 Como (ITA)

Address

Fino Mornasco via Garibaldi 88

Contact

+39 3409447428 federico.izzop@gmail.com

About

25 years old, builder of lego. 3+ years of experience designing stuff.

A strong, structured, efficient, detail- and impact-oriented digital designer, with focus on UI and DataViz.

Languages

Italian

First Language

English

C2 Level - Fluent TOEIC test: 845/900

Spanish

Fluent

Education

2019-ongoing

Politecnico di Milano

Communication Design Master Degree

2016-2019

Politecnico di Milano

Communication Design Bachelor Degree

Softwares

Design

Adobe Creative Cloud, Figma

DataViz

RawGraph, Gephi, Qgis, D3js, Excel

Coding

Html, Css, Javascript, P5, D3, Jquery, Python, Github, Nodejs, Wordpress

Miscellaneus

Apple iWorks suite, Microsoft Office, Farrago

Work Experience

2019-ongoing

Website builder

Realization of webistes as a freelance designer for Tropico.Zone and EditionsMilano.

2018

Accomodation office @PoliMi

2017-18

Brand and Website

Brand image & website for a three-day educational event Pretest BVS @ PoliMi